Craig Seymour Collection, 1968-2006 SC 144
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 5. Audiovisual (excluding interviews)
  - 5.2. Commercial media, Nearly 1,000 CDs of commercially released audio is included in this collection. The CDs are a mixture of published and unpublished releases. The unpublished releases are primarily promotional copies sent out in advance of an album release for review. The unpublished record
    - Jon B. // Jon B., 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12506
      Edmonds Music
    - Media Lynching of African Americans (Session 7, Essence 2004 Empowerment Series) // Michael Eric Dyson, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12507
    - From the News Rack to the Book Rack: Finding stories that make great books (and recognizing those that don't) (The 2004 Nieman Conference on Narrative Journalism) // Dawn Davis, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12508
    - Beep Me 911 (featuring 702 and Magoo) // Missy Misdemeanor Elliott, 1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12509
      The Gold Mind, Inc.
    - Sampler // Hustlechild, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12510
    - Champagne (Johnny Douglas Remix) // Salt-N-Pepa, 1996; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12511
    - "Movin' On" [single] // Mya, 1998; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12512
    - Uh Huh [single] // Terri & Monica, 1993; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12513
      Sony Music
    - All Day, All Night [remixes] // Stephanie Mills, 1992; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12514
    - It's All About You (Not About Me) [single] // Tracie, 1999; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12515
    - Can't Nobody Hold Me Down [remix] // Puff Daddy, 1996-1997; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12516
      Bad Boy Entertainment
    - Kamaal The Abstract [Album advance] // Q-Tip, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12517
    - Nine Lives // AZ, 2001; 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12518
    - Nivea [Advance copy] // Nivea, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12519
    - Chapter 1: Love, Pain & Forgiveness [Advance copy] // Syleena Johnson, 1 Audio Disc
      CD 12520
- 6. Photographs
  - Mary J. Blige, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012184
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001481
  - Chocolate Genius, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012185
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001482
  - N'Dea Davenport, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012186
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001483
  - Aretha Franklin, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012187
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001484
  - MC Lyte, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012188
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001485
  - Nicole, 1996; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012189
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001486
  - The Rolling Stones, 1996; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012190
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001487
  - The Smashing Pumpkins, 1989; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012191
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001488
  - The Smashing Pumpkins, 1998-04; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012192
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001489
  - Sylvester, 1998-05; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012193
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001490
  - Trin-i-tee 5:7, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012194
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001491
  - Xscape, 1998; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012195
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001492
  - Xscape - Traces of My Lipstick, 1998; 1 Slide color
    SL??
  - Xscape, 1 Slide color
  - Ying Yang Twins, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
    PA012196
    http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001493
- 7. Magazines, promotional materials, and miscellaneous clippings
  - 7.1. Sister 2 Sister
    - Sister 2 Sister, June 1994; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, October 1994; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, December 1994; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, February 1995; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, April 1995; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, May 1995; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, June 1995; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, August 1995; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, September 1995; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, November 1995; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, February 1996; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, March 1996; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, April 1996; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, June 1996; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, July 1996; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, September 1996; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, November 1996; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, December 1996; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, January 1997; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, May 1997; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, June 1997; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, July 1997; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, August 1997; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, September 1997; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, December 1997; 1 magazine (Box 8)
    - Sister 2 Sister, January 1998; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, February 1998; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, March 1998; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, April 1998; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, May 1998; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, July 1998; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, August 1998; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, September 1998; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, October 1998; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, February 1999; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, March 1999; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, April 1999; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, May 1999; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, June 1999; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, July 1999; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, August 1999; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, September 1999; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, November 1999; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, December 1999; 1 magazine (Box 9)
    - Sister 2 Sister, January 2000; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, February 2000; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, March 2000; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, April 2000; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, June 2000; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, August 2000; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, December 2000; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, January 2001; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, February 2001; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, April 2001; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, May 2001; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, August 2001; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, September 2001; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, October 2001; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, November 2001; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, December 2001; 1 magazine (Box 10)
    - Sister 2 Sister, February 2002; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, April 2002; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, May 2002; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, June 2002; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, July 2002; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, August 2002; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister: Lisa LeftEye Lopes Farewell Issue, August 2002; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, October 2002; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, February 2003; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, May 2003; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, October 2003; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, November 2003; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, March 2004; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, May 2004; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, April 2005; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, June 2005; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, July 2005; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, March 2006; 1 magazine (Box 11)
    - Sister 2 Sister, February 2007; 1 magazine (Box 11)
  - 7.2. Miscellaneous magazines and clippings
    - Blues & Soul, No. 152, Jan. 21-Feb 3, 1975; 1 magazine (Box 12)
    - DJ, April 1998; 1 magazine
    - Goldmine, October 23, 1998; 1 magazine (Box 13 OS, Folder 20)
    - Grand Royal, 1997; 1 magazine (Box 12)
    - Honey, March 2002; 1 magazine (Box 12)
    - Honey, December 2003/January 2004; 1 magazine (Box 12)
    - Players, Vol. 4, No. 5 [RESTRICTED], 1977-10; 1 magazine (Box 12)
    - Players, Vol. 4, No. 11 [RESTRICTED], 1978-04; 1 magazine (Box 12)
    - Rap Pages, Oct 1997; 1 magazine
    - Rolling Stone, June 2 1994; 1 magazine
    - Source, Jan 1998; 1 magazine
    - Vibe (24 issues), Feb 1994-Dec 2004; 24 magazines
    - The Wire, Issue 114, August 1993; 1 magazine (Box 12)
    - XXL: 1997 premier issue, May 2002; 1 magazine
    - Jon Pareles, "How Rap Moves to Television's Beat," The New York Times, January 14, 1990; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 1)
    - Jon Pareles, "Rap: Slick, Violent, Nasty and, Maybe, Hopeful," The New York Times, June 17, 1990; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 2)
    - Joan Morgan, "The Nigga Ya Hate To Love," The Village Voice, July 17, 1990; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 3)
    - Joan Morgan, "Gangsta Fairy Tale," The Village Voice, September 24, 1991; 1 clipping (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Nelson George, "Two Detroit Sisters," The Village Voice, October 8, 1991; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 4)
    - Robert Christgau and Greg Tate, "Chuck D: All Over The Map" and Marshall Berman, "Bass in Your Face," The Village Voice, October 22, 1991; 2 clippings (Box 13 OS, Folder 5)
    - Nelson George, "Michael Bivins: Boy to Man," The Village Voice, November 5, 1991; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 6)
    - Mim Udovitch, "Improper," The Village Voice, November 12, 1991; 1 clipping (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Nelson George, "Survival of the Illest," The Village Voice, February 11, 1992; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 7)
    - Cheryl L. Coward, "'Quiet Storm' creator led a quiet Gay life," The Washington Blade, April 3, 1992; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 8)
    - Nelson George, "New Jack L.A.," The Village Voice, April 21, 1992; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 9)
    - Chuck Eddy, "Dressed for Success" and Milo Miles, "Riches Untold," The Village Voice, May 26, 1992 (Box 13 OS, Folder 10)
    - Ben Mapp, "Soul to Soul Brothers," The Village Voice, July 21, 1992; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 11)
    - Rob Tannenbaum, "Not Phat, But Fat," The Village Voice, April 27, 1993; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 12)
    - "Rockbeat," The Village Voice, July 6, 1993; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 13)
    - Nelson George, "How I Spent My Vacation" and Colson Whitehead, "Sgt. Rapper's," The Village Voice, July 27, 1993; 2 clippings (Box 13 OS, Folder 14)
    - James T. Jones IV, "Rap on Rap," USA Today, August 5, 1993; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 15)
    - "Rockbeat: Abandon Shit," The Village Voice, September 28, 1993; 1 clipping (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Richard Harrington, "Shooting Back at Gangsta Rap," Washington Post, November 14, 1993; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 16)
    - RJ Smith, "America's Hoopride," The Village Voice, December 21, 1993; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 17)
    - Rickey Wright, "Noblesse o' Blige," Washington City Paper, May 16, 1997; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 18)
    - Touré, "Best Rapper Alive," The Village Voice, August 5, 1997; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 19)
    - The Times-Picayune, July 4, 2004; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 21)
    - Eric Weisbard, "The Ancestors of Pop," The New York Times Book Review, October 31, 2004; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 22)
    - Sasha Frere-Jones, "1+1+1=1," The New Yorker, January 10, 2005; 1 clipping (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Films - music, 2005-04-29; Printouts from several websites with info related to the 1971 Academy Awards. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Michael Musto, "La Dolce Musto," The Village Voice, undated; 1 clipping (Box 13 OS, Folder 23)
    - Nelson George, "Pop Life," The Village Voice, undated; 1 clipping (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Edna Gunderson, "A record of L.A. gang life," USA Today, undated; 1 clipping (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Paula Nessick & Bunty Matthias, "Dream Deferred," The Face, undated; 1 clipping (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - James Bernard, "Down on the Corner", undated; 1 clipping (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Clipping photograph of Roxanne Shante and Kareem, undated; 1 clipping (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Village Voice - correspondence, undated; 1 letter (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 7.3. Promotional materials
    - Luther Vandross in Concert promotional book, 1985; 1 book (Box 13 OS, Folder 24)
    - Luther Vandross Give Me The Reason. In Europe 1987. Promotional book., 1 book (Box 13 OS, Folder 25)
    - Luther Vandross in Concert promotional book, 1988; 1 book (Box 13 OS, Folder 26)
    - Mary J. Blige promotional packet for How Stella Got Her Groove Back soundtrack and live album The Tour, 1998; 1 Folder (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Mary J. Blige, 2022-05-27; 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
        PA012197
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001494
    - Janet Jackson promotional packet for Teen Feature Story, 1989; 1 Folder (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Janet, 1 Photograph color; 8 x 10 in.
        PA012198
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001495
    - Monica promotional packet, 1998; 1 Folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Monica, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
        PA012199
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001496
      - Monica, 1 Photograph b&w; 8 x 10 in.
        PA012200
        http://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/images/VAD5465/VAD5465-001497
    - Flyers + greeting card, 1994-2002, undated; 1 Folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Janet Jackson poster, undated; 1 Poster (Box POS 5)
      POS 182
    - Promotional cardboard cutout for Rudy Ray Moore's Greatest Hits album, 1996 (Box 13 OS, Folder 27)
    - Soul Merchant Guerrilla Tribe CD sleeve and insert (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Only includes 8.5 x 11" outer CD sleeve and liner notes insert. Disc is not present.